When you meet real military people in chat roulette, it’s
Вот когда в чат-рулетке встречаются
interesting
реально военные, с ними интересно
to talk to them, yes, but you can see that
поговорить, да, но ты же видно, что
you have it expressed.  Let me tell you,
выраженный у тебя. Давайте расскажу,
ask questions.  Your face
задавайте вопрос. У тебя лицо
even looks scared, damn it.
перепуганное даже, блин, какое-то.
Ask a question.  Look, the
Задавайте вопрос. Ты посмотри на тебе
uniform doesn't suit you.  It's obvious that you, in short,
форма не сидит. Видно, что ты, короче,
damn, dressed her, damn, just for this, for
блин, её одел, блин, так для этого, для
fun, right?
прикола, правда?
Hello.  Hello.  Why did you
Здравствуйте. Здравствуйте. А зачем ты
thin out if you are not a military man?
выредился, если ты не военный?
Oh, my dear.
О, сраждана.
No, why?
Не, ну зачем?
In terms of?  Well, if you were a military man,
В смысле? Ну вот если ты военный был,
right?  Here the military wears uniform.  Why did you
да? Вот военные носят форму. А зачем ты
thin out if you are not a military man?  And why
выредился, если ты не военный? А с чего
should I dress up?
я буду выряжаться?
Well, look, you have such a funny face
Ну вот смотри, у тебя лицо смешное
, clearly not military.  Yes, okay,
такое, явно не военное. Да, да ладно, да
okay.  Chevrons are not worn on the head
ладно. Шевроны на голове не носят
.  Is it true?
шевроны. Правда?
I dressed it especially for chat roulette, right?
Я специально для чата рулетки одел, да?
So I'm asking, why do you dress
То есть я спрашиваю, зачем ты одеваешься
in a suit if you're not a military man?
в костюм, если ты не военный?
Come on, you're not a military man.  Where are you
Да ладно, да ты же не военный. Откуда вы
fighting from?  Well, you're not a military man.  Explain.
боете? Ну ты же не военный. Объясни.
No, look, when you
Нет, смотри, вот когда в чат-рулетке
meet real military people in chat roulette, and it’s
встречаются реально военные, и с ними
interesting to talk to them, yes, but you can
интересно поговорить, да, но ты же
see that you’re cut out.  Let me
видно, что выреженный у тебя. Давайте
tell you, ask questions.  Your face
расскажу, задавайте вопросы. У тебя лицо
even looks scared, damn it.
перепуганное даже, блин, какое-то.
Ask a question.  And look, the
Задавайте вопрос. И посмотри, на тебе
uniform doesn't suit you.  It's obvious that you, in short,
форма не сидит. Видно, что ты, короче,
damn, dressed her, damn, just for this, for
блин, её одел, блин, так для этого, для
fun,
прикола,
right?  What do you look like?
правда? Как ты выглядишь?
Okay, I destroyed it.
ладно, уничтожил.
Oh well, hello again.  What are you saying,
Да ладно, ещё раз здравствуйте. Что вы,
that you ran away then?  I don't care, you know. I did
что убежал тогда? Я ничего так вы Я же
n't serve.  So you ran away?  Well then
не служил. Так что ты убежал? Ну так
explain.  Well, I didn't serve correctly.
объясни. Так, правильно не служил.
Explain why you dress like this? Why do you
Объясни, зачем ты как Зачем ты как
dress like this?  I'm a eater.  I'm in disguise.  Yes.
одеваешься? Я жеряй. Я же ряженый. Да.
So why are you running away?  Be responsible for your
Так зачем ты убегаешь? Отвечай за свой
words.  Well, I'm in disguise.  So dressed up.
базар. Так я же ряженый. Так ряженый.
Answer.  Why are you dressed up?
Ответь. Зачем ты ряженый?
I don't understand why I'm dressed up.  Well,
Я не понимаю, почему я ряженый. Ну
because you... Look at yourself.  You're not
потому что ты Ты посмотри на себя. Ты не
dressed according to regulations, like, damn.  In terms of?
по уставу одет, типа ты, блин. В смысле?
In terms of?  The risers looked.  Look in
В смысле? Вставы смотрели. Посмотри
Russian.  Who?  What university do you attend?   University
российски. Кто? Какой у тебя вуз?
?  Yes.  What do you mean, university?  Take this A vsu type
Вуз? Да. В смысле вуз? Вз это А всу типа
A in the sense that you have a part?  Not a university.
А в смысле вы имеете часть? Не вуз. Вуз
What university do you attend?  If you served, you
у тебя какой? Если ты служил, у тебя вуз
should have a university, right?
должен быть, а?
Damn, something like 700.
Блин, что-то там 700.
What does university stand for?
Как расшифровывается вуз?
Military specialty, yes, you
Военная специальность, да, имеете в
mean?  How does it stand for?   University
виду? Как она расшифровывается?
.  The word university.  Military specialty.
Вуз. Слово вуз. Военная специальность.
You mean?  How does it
Вы имеете в виду? Как она
stand for?  University.
расшифровывается? Вуз.
Well, how should I know?  I am a contract soldier.
Ну я я откуда знаю? Я контрактник.
How would I know?  This is how a contract soldier
Откуда я знаю? Так у контрактника вуз
writes his university.  Your military ID
пишется. У тебя в военном билете вуз
says your university.  I'll take a look now.
пишется. Сейчас посмотрю.
real.  University, university.
реальный. Вуз вузву.
Okay,
Так,
now.  Don't you remember your
сейчас. Ты не помнишь свой
university?  Don't you remember what university you went to?  In
вуз? Ты не помнишь, какой у тебя вуз? В
terms of?  What kind of
смысле? Что за
university is this?
вуз?
There is no higher education institution here.
ВЧУЗ здесь нет вуса. Слова
Even words.  Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
даже. Так, так, так, так, так.
What?  Wait, maybe I'm opening the wrong page
Что? Подожди, может я не ту страницу
?
открываю?
You have opened the wrong page of your life.
Ты не ту страницу жизни своей открыл.
What the hell kind of university is this
Что за вуз-то,
?  Maybe I'm
блин? Может, я
drowning?
топлю?
I'm learning,
Усву,
I'm learning.  Maybe you are saying it wrong?
усвус. Может, вы неправильно говорите?
Maybe you speak some Ukrainian?
Может, по-украински что-то говорите?
Where is the word university?  Not here.  What words
Где слово вуз? Здесь нет. Какие слова
are there?  What words are there?  There are
там есть? Какие слова там есть? Там
many other words.  Well, let's have some like this.
много других слов. Ну давай вот какие.
Let's find a university.
Давай найдём вуз.
What page should the military ID
А какая страница военного билета должна
be on?  On page eleven you have.  On the
быть? На одиннадцатой странице у вас. На
eleventh.  Fine.  Maybe I just didn't
одиннадцатой. Хорошо. Может я просто не
open page eleven.
открыл одиннадцатую страницу.
Well, I
А вот
found the university.  Exactly. How do I know what I have
нашёл. Точно е. Откуда знаю, что у меня
written there?  I think I have it on
там написано? Кажется, у меня на
page eleven, yes, it is
одиннадцатой странице, да, есть именно
on page eleven.  And what do
на одиннадцатой странице. И что там у
you have written on page eleven?
тебя написано на одиннадцатой странице?
Which university?
Какой вуз?
9 0 A. What does it mean?   I
9 0 А. Что она означает?
don't know how I know.  What is a university?
Не знаю, откуда знаю. А что такое вуз?
What is written in your
Вот что у тебя в оди на одиннадцатой
university on page eleven?  But you served.   It
странице вуз написано? Ты же служил.
says university.
Написано вуз.
Eh, the full code designation of the university.  Yes.
Ээ полное кодовое обозначение вуз. Да.
Well, what does that mean?
Ну что означает?
That's all.  Dictate it in numbers.  Right now I'm
Вот и всё. Продиктуй по цифрах. Сейчас я
just okay.  Taste.  Three nines, three
прямо О'кей. Вкус. Три девятки, три
zeros.  That's
ноля. Вот и
all.  Limited fitness for military service.
всё. Ограниченно годный к воинской.
[laughter]
[смех]
Why are
А что
you laughing?  Limited fitness for military
смеёшься? Ограниченно годный к воинской
service without military training.  Here are three
службе без военной подготовки. Вот три
nines, 3rd university.  This university is a
девятки 3 вуз. Это вуз - это
military registration specialty, you understand?
военно-учётная специальность, понимаешь?
And here
А
I am, look, three nines 3:0.  This is what is
я смотри, три девятки 3:0. Вот это в
limited in Russia as being fit for military
российско ограничено годной к воинской
service without military training.
службе без военной подготовки. Также
There is also no military
отсутствует какая-либо военная
specialty.
специальность.
Although the specialty is
Хотя специальность есть
military.  All.
военная. Все.
Can you explain why you are of
А можешь объяснить, почему ты
limited fitness for permanent residence? Well, do you have
ограниченно годный безменно по Ну у тебя
some kind of deviations or
какие-то отклонения или
something?  The second
что? Второй
time, the first time, when he got shy and
раз, первый раз, когда он застеснялся,
ran away, it was just funny.  Now
убежал, это было просто смешно. Сейчас
I generally
это вообще
found pages in Us once.  Oh, indeed,
Ус находила страниц. Ой, действительно,
there is a
тут есть
university here.  Three nines zero.  I
вуз. Три девятки нуля. Я
googled and they actually have three nines 3.
гуглю реально у них три девятки 3.
Well, it is limited to those fit for military service
Ну ограничено годной к воинской службе
without military training.  Also, this is
без военной подготовки. Такжест это
generally a like, subscription, comment.  It
вообще лайк, подписка комент. Бомбезно
was amazing to subscribe to my Telegram right
было підпишись на мій Telegram прямо
away.  Here it is.  And
зараз. Ось він. А
the priest is even more and more important.  YouTube
попик це дуже и дуже важливо. YouTube
is banning us through karger.
заганяе нас через каргер в тньовий бан.
And too many videos are not shown to people
І дуже багато відео не показуется людям
regularly, and information about the stream is not shown
вчасно, не показуется інформація про
.  Therefore, in order for us to get a
стрими. Тому для того, щоб ми мали
quick connection, sign up right
оперативный зв'язок підпишиться прямо
away.  And the priest there in the telegram okmdeo is
зараз. А попик там в телеграмі окмдео ще
still useful and useful information and we are
теж цікава и корисна информация и мы
obliged to work with you to maintain a consistent
повинні з вами тримати постійний
operational connection.  It doesn’t matter
оперативный зв'язок. Незалежно від того,
if YouTube shows you about it.  Glory to
чи покаже вам про цей YouTube. Слава
Ukraine!  Subscribe.
Україні! Підпишись.